[{
    "theme": "Minimalismo",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "cold",
            "answers": ["frío"]
        },
        {
            "question": "cute / pretty",
            "answers": ["lindo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I cheer up / I get happy",
            "answers": ["me alegro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "dwelling / housing",
            "answers": ["habitación"]
        },
        {
            "question": "my case",
            "answers": ["mi caso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "gift / present",
            "answers": ["regalo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "clothes",
            "answers": ["ropa"]
        },
        {
            "question": "shoes",
            "answers": ["zapatos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "pen / stylus",
            "answers": ["stylo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "minimalist",
            "answers": ["minimalista"]
        },
        {
            "question": "beautiful / handsome",
            "answers": ["hermoso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to clean",
            "answers": ["limpiar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to control",
            "answers": ["controlar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "house / home",
            "answers": ["casa"]
        },
        {
            "question": "sister",
            "answers": ["hermana"]
        },
        {
            "question": "book",
            "answers": ["libro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "lack / missing",
            "answers": ["falta"]
        }
    ]
}]
